http://www.northlandcabinets.com/privacy-policy

About UsMeet the TeamTestimonialsEmployment ApplicationGalleryKitchenBathLiving SpaceOffice - Work SpaceDrop ZoneBefore & AfterShowroomVideoOur ProcessDesignPlanningDraftingRemodeling & InstallationResidential & CommercialProductsWood SelectionsGreen ProductsFinishesHardware & AccessoriesCountertopsDesign CenterContact Us
763.424.2775
About UsMeet the TeamTestimonialsEmployment ApplicationGalleryKitchenBathLiving SpaceOffice - Work SpaceDrop ZoneBefore & AfterShowroomVideoOur ProcessDesignPlanningDraftingRemodeling & InstallationResidential & CommercialProductsWood SelectionsGreen ProductsFinishesHardware & AccessoriesCountertopsDesign CenterContact Us
763.424.2775
About UsMeet the TeamTestimonialsEmployment ApplicationGalleryKitchenBathLiving SpaceOffice - Work SpaceDrop ZoneBefore & AfterShowroomVideoOur ProcessDesignPlanningDraftingRemodeling & InstallationResidential & CommercialProductsWood SelectionsGreen ProductsFinishesHardware & AccessoriesCountertopsDesign CenterContact Us
privacy policyThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.NorthlandCabinets.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
763.424.2775
9461 Deerwood Lane North
Maple Grove MN 55369
Home
About Us
Gallery
Our Process
Products
Northland Cabinets, Inc. All rights reserved.
Sitemap | Site Credits | Privacy Policy
